By now, many of you all have seen my episode of Surrounded, One Black Radical, Surrounded by 20 Black Conservatives.
And I know everybody who watched it has many thoughts.
Someone in the comments did say, wow, it's a shock that Amanda Seale didn't know how to debate.
And at first I was offended by that.
And I was like, what video did you watch?
And then I actually watched the whole video last night with the Seale squad.
And I realized, oh, yeah, I'm not debating.
And the irony about this was that it's not that I didn't know how to debate.
It's that I just chose not to debate because the claims that I stated are not up for debate.
Reparations are deserved for everyone who is the descendant of shadow slavery, as well as a number of other injustices, particularly in the United States, that have been supplanted upon Black Americans.
Black on Black crime is not real.
It's a concept that was created to further the ideology that Black people are somehow less civil, that we are savage, that we are less human.
And thus require more policing needing to be sequestered.
The continued proliferation of Black on Black crime as an actual real concept is actually Black on Black crime.
It is the weaponizing of Black people against Black people.
Systemic racism is not up for debate.
It is what it is.
And lastly, no, Black conservatism does not make any concessions or room or care for the working class.
Actually, the concept of Black conservatives is literally an oxymoron.
When I walked into that room and I saw the people that were there and how many of them were young people, I didn't want to debate them.
And I was dealing with people who are deeply affected by indoctrination and by self-hatred.
And I wanted to show them the ways in which they had been misled to being able to show up for themselves and for their people.
And of course, they're only a portion of this project.
The true audience is not who you're debating, but who's watching.
And trying to get information and concepts to them that are being actively impeded.
And that felt far more valuable than just being right.
Amen.